Guide to the Gay Liberation Front records, 1971-1972
Gay Liberation Front records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay Liberation Front records, 1971-1972
7805
Gay Liberation Front.
.3 cubic feet
Organizational records, correspondence, and printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the organization including newsletters, financial records, correspondence, minutes, fliers, notes, and programs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the organization including newsletters, financial records, correspondence, minutes, fliers, notes, and programs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gay Liberation Front.
Subjects:
Gay men -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State) -- Rochester.; Lesbians -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State) -- Rochester.
Places:
New York (State) -- Rochester
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records
NOTES
Arrangement and description of the Gay Liberation Front records, #7805 made possible in part by a grant from the Documentary Heritage Program of the New York State Archives, a program of the State Education Department
CONTAINER LIST
- Gay Liberation Front- University of Rochester Journal, October 21, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Gay Liberation Front Fliers/ Posters
  - Spring Dance, May 6, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gay Festival, October 22-24, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 'Hex' A Gay Liberation Dance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4 copies
- Gay Liberation Front- Agendas, Organized Material, Publications
  - Empty Fundraising Envelope: New York Gay Rights Office, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agenda Gay Liberation Front, May - October 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agenda Program Committee, July - November 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agenda Steering Committee, October 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gay Tour Slide Show, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Slide List with Captions
  - Consciousness-Raising Groups, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Questionnaire, Letter, Agenda (GALS and GUYS)
  - Anniversary Festival schedule, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Music: "What A Great Thing It Is", Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Poster: Gay Festival, October 22-24, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - What Does it Mean to Live?, September 19, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Collection of quotes.
  - What Does it Mean to Just Exist, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, April 1971; June 1971; August 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Note Cards Listing Gay Bars and Baths, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - What Do I Want From A Counselor???, October 3, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter to Dr. (Laud) Humphries from GLF Staff, May 13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Thanking him for his recent visit to the Rochester GLF and inviting him to visit again
  - List of names and telephone numbers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - List of volunteers for office staffing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Schedule, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Office Calendar, Summer 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes peoples' shifts/ schedules
  - GLF Office Staff Information Sheet, June 13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Information of Gary Sicurella
  - GLF Office Family Training, June 13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes on what was decided during the meeting.
  - Questionnaire, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Lists a number of hypothetical situations an LGBTQ person may find him/herself in.
  - Memo to Dr. Laud Humphries re: Sunday "Workshop", Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Outlining what the GLF hopes Dr. Humphries will speak about during his talk called "Counseling Ethics and Techniques"
  - Instructions for contacting Office Staff volunteers with contact information of volunteers., June 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Office phone answering guidelines, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Information about upcoming organizational session.
  - A Committee of Chairmen flowchart, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Office Family Notes, Summer 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Information on leadership positions within GLF and on how the organization is run.
  - GLF Steering Committee Flow Chart, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter to Larry, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Edits to a document
  - Minutes Program Committee, June 1971; July 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memo to Gary Ljunquist, June 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    26 September '71 AGE (Under-age gays, gays over 30); From: Walt
  - Poster Sketch, "VD's A Bummer!", June 20, Year not stated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memo to Gary Ljunquist re: August '71 Please Touch Meeting; From: Walt, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter Budget, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memo to Gary Ljunquist re: 26 September '71 AGE (Under-age gays, gays over 30), from Walt, June 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dulaney, Touch Program Practice Session, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Publications
  - Gay Liberation is a struggle against sexism, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fifth Freedom Newsletter of the Niagara Frontier Gay Community v.3 no.14, November 30, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaire- Gay Marriage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Empty Closet No. 8 (Two Copies), Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Empty Closet No. 5 (Incomplete), June 29, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Empty Closet No. 6, July 13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Empty Closet No. 7, July 27, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)